(Howard:)I mean, we have needs and...
(Bernadette:)So you've been seeing
other girls?
(Howard:)Well, not real girls.
(Bernadette:)Does that mean slutty trolls?
(Penny:)You know, you look thirsty.
(Penny:)I brought you some iced tea.
Thank you.
(Penny:)It's passion fruit,
new on the menu.
I know. I work here.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, you're right. Doy.
So, Howard,
yay or nay?
(Howard:)Isn't there somewhere else
you can be?
(Penny:)Not where I can hear you guys.
(Penny:)Okay, fine.
(Howard:)I'll admit, there are dark,
sordid little corners
(Howard:)of the Internet
where the name Wolowizard
(Howard:)is whispered in hushed tones.
(Howard:)The only reason I go there,
(Howard:)the only reason
I've ever gone there
(Howard:)is because I don't have
a real woman in my life.
(Howard:)You happy?
Yeah, that'll hold me
for a while.
(Bernadette:)Howard, you did have
a real woman.
(Bernadette:)I was right there
in the next room
(Bernadette:)while you were clicking
that troll's brains out.